Switchmen's Union of North America Records 5034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (Great Northern-Kansas City Terminal) (Box 28)
  - Agreement and Strike File: K and I Bridge Company - Form contract (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kansas City, Fort Scott and Memphis - Wages and regulations, 1901 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kansas City Southern Railway - General, 1913-1934 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kansas City Southern Railway - Miscellaneous file, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kansas City Southern Railway - General, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kansas City Southern Railway - General Session, minutes and miscellaneous correspondence, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kansas City Southern Railway - Milwaukee Coordination, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kansas City Southern Railway - Memorandum agreement and correspondence, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kansas City Southern - Vacation agreement and dispute, 1944-1947 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kansas City Southern Railway - Rival Unionism Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen-Switchmen's Union of North America, 1948- 1949 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Agreement and Strike file: Kansas City Terminal - Organizing, 1941-1944 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    A-1 - E-1. Organizing
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kansas City Terminal - Agreement and related correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kansas City Terminal - Strike file, 1952-1953 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kansas City Terminal - Agreement, miscellaneous correspondence, rules, rates, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kansas City Terminal - General, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kansas City Terminal - Wage section and notice, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 47)
- Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (Kennecott Copper Corporation-Litchfield and Madison) (Box 29)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kennecott Copper Corporation - 1941 agreement, wages and working conditions (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Agreement and Strike file: Kennecott Copper Corporation - Agreement, wages and working conditions, 1942 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kennecott Copper Corporation - General, 1944-1945 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kennecott Copper Corporation - Agreements, 1946-1947 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kennecott Copper Corporation - Wage negotiations, 1948-1949 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kennecott Copper Corporation - Agreements, 1948-1949 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Agreement and Strike file: Kennecott Copper Corporation - Memorandum Agreement (rejected), correspondence, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kennecott Copper Corporation - Memorandum Agreement and negotiating, schedule, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kennecott Copper Corporation - Application of agreement, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Agreement and Strike file: Kennecott Copper Corporation - Wage Negotiations, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kennecott Copper Corporation - Negotiation schedule, etcetera, 1951-1952 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kennecott Copper Corporation - Agreements, 1951-1959 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    Correspondence. 1951-1953, 1955- 1956, 1959
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kennecott Copper Corporation - Copper, 1956-1957 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Kennecott Copper Corporation - Agreements, correspondence on strike, 1961-1967 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    Correspondence. 1961, 1964, 1967
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lackawanna Steel Plant - Request for rate of wages (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Shore and Michigan Southern - Rates of pay, 1901-1902 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Shore and Michigan Southern - Working condition proposal, working schedule, pay rate (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Shore and Michigan Southern - Miscellaneous correspondence, report of General Grievance Committees, 1912-1931 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Shore and Michigan Southern - Minutes of sub-committee, 1914-1915 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Agreement and Strike file: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Schedule of working conditions, correspondence on 1924-1927 agreement, 1923 pay rates, 1919- 1927 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    1919, 1923-1924, 1927
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - General chairman correspondence, 1919-1923 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - General Chairman's correspondence, 1925-1928 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - General Correspondence, 1932-1936 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - General Correspondence, 1935-1943 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    9a. Correspondence
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - General Correspondence, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - General Correspondence, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - General Correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Agreement and Strike file: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Seniority dispute, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    Correspondence. September 1937
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Seniority Dispute, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    Correspondence. October-November 1937
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Correspondence on cases (Keeley and Landgreen), 1939 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Correspondence on cases (Keeley and Landgreen), 1940-1941 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Correspondence on transfer work, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Correspondence on wages dispute, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - General correspondence, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - General Correspondence, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - General Correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - General correspondence, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Agreements and related correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Agreement and strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Vacation agreement and related correspondence, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - General, 1949-1950 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Vacation claims, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Memorandum agreement, interim agreement, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer (LST and T) - SUNA 10-W between Switchmen's Union of North America and LST and T, 1950- 1966 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    Correspondence, manuscript.
  - Agreement and Strike file: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Agreement, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Productivity increase, miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Agreement an Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Strike authorization, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Booking car allowance, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Change in 1955 agreement, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Reapplying for foreman's rate, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Seniority of switchmen, 1956-1957 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - General correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - General Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - General, 1959-1967 (Box 29, Folder 53)
    Correspondence. 1959, 1967
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake superior Terminal and Transfer - Wage section 6 notice, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer - Rules, regulations, schedules (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lehigh Valley Railway - Rules, rates and schedules, correspondence, 1913-1928 (Box 29, Folder 56)
    Correspondence. 1913, 1914-1921, 1928
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lehigh Valley - General, rates, rules and regulations, 1918-1919 (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lehigh Valley - General, 1919 (Box 29, Folder 58)
    Correspondence. May-October 1919
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lehigh Valley - General, 1920-1930 (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lehigh Valley - Supplemental agreement, schedule, rates and rules, general correspondence, 1931-1933 (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lehigh Valley - Miscellaneous, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lehigh Valley - Miscellaneous, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lehigh Valley - Miscellaneous, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 63)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lehigh Valley, 1952-1953 (Box 29, Folder 64)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lehigh Valley - Abandonment, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 65)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Lehigh Valley - Correspondence on award 1763, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 66)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Litchfield and Madison Railway - Agreement, 1918 (Box 29, Folder 67)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Litchfield and Madison - Miscellaneous, agreement, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 68)
- Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (Long Island Railroad-Manufacturers' Railroad) (Box 30)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Long Island Railroad - Miscellaneous, 1921-1948 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Correspondence. 1921, 1947-1948
  - Agreement and Strike File: Louisville and Arkansas - Strike file, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Louisville and Nashville - United States Railroad Labor Board dispute, 1922-1925 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    2a. Correspondence
  - Agreement and Strike File: Louisville and Nashville - Agreement, correspondence regarding United States Railroad Labor Board, 1923 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Louisville and Nashville - Correspondence regarding United States Railroad Labor Board, 1923-1924 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Louisville and Nashville - Docket case 3975 (United States Railroad Labor Board) SUNA versus Louisville and Nashville, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    SUNA: Switchmen's Union of North America. Manuscript
  - Agreement and Strike File: Louisville and Nashville - Correspondence United States Railroad Labor Board, 1924-1925 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Louisville and Nashville - General organizing, 1927-1928 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Louisville and Nashville - Disputes National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1935-1938 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    Correspondence. 1935, 1938
  - Agreement and Strike File: Louisville and Nashville - Disputes National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1938 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Louisville and Nashville - Disputes National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Louisville and Nashville - Miscellaneous, 1941-1944 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Agreement and Strike file: Louisville and Nashville - Rival unionism, Switchmen's Union of North America and Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Louisville and Nashville - General disputes, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Louisville and Nashville - General dispute, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Louisville and Nashville - General Grievance Association, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Louisville and Nashville - Switchmen's Union of North America versus Louisville and Nashville Number 2628 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction Railway - Memorandum of proceedings, 1921 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction Railway - Agreement, vacation agreement, working papers of agreement, 1939-1952 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    Correspondence. 1935, 1949, 1952.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - Agreement with revisions, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - Original third carbon of agreement (SUNA and Los Angeles Junction Railway), 1952 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - N.L.A.B. Case L-1062 (cancelled), 1952 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    NLAB = NLRB? Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - List of claims, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - Correspondence on claims, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - claims (pending, withdrawn, etcetera), 1951-1952 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - Cases paid or settled, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    A-2 - D-2. Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - Working papers on agreement, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - General correspondence, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - General Correspondence, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - General Correspondence, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - General Correspondence, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - General correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - National Railroad Adjustment Board L-1189 (no award), 1955 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - National Railroad Adjustment Board L-1187 (no award), 1955 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - National Railroad Adjustment Board 1183, 1184, 1185 (no award), 1955 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - 15 claims to be conferenced, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - Letter of understanding, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - Resignation of General Chairman Harrell, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - Case SUNA-1W, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - National Railroad Adjustment Board L-1190 (no award), 1955-1956 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    7a. Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - Los Angeles Junction representation election, propaganda, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    7b. Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - Increase arbitrary allowance, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - Joint submission agreement, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - General correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - SUNA-34-W, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Junction - Wage Notice, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Los Angeles Railway Company - 27 claims, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - Agreement and Strike File, 1943-1958 (Box 30, Folder 49)
    Correspondence. 1943, 1948, 1952-1958
  - Agreement and Strike File: Mason City and Clear Lake - Agreement and amendment, 1952-1956 (Box 30, Folder 50)
    Correspondence. 1952, 1956
  - Agreement and Strike File: Mason City and Clearlake - Wage negotiations, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Mason City and Clearlake - Revision of schedule, 1957-1959 (Box 30, Folder 52)
    Correspondence. 1957, 1959.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Manufacturers' Railway - Agreements and correspondence, 1917-1943 (Box 30, Folder 53)
    Correspondence. 1917, 1919-1920, 1922, 1925, 1943
  - Agreement and Strike File: Manufacturers' Railroad - Correspondence regarding wage negotiations, 1919-1921 (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - Agreement and Strike file: Manufacturers' Railroad - Correspondence regarding wage negotiations, 1923-1924 (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Manufacturers' Railroad - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1925 (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - Agreement and Strike file: Manufacturers' Railroad - Correspondence and agreement, 1925 (Box 30, Folder 57)
    Correspondence. March-August 1925
  - Agreement and Strike File: Manufacturers' Railroad - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 30, Folder 58)
    Correspondence. November-December 1925
  - Agreement and Strike File: Manufacturers' Railroad - Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Manufacturers' Railroad - Wage and rule demands, 1926 (Box 30, Folder 60)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Manufacturers' Railroad - Miscellaneous, 1932-1938 (Box 30, Folder 61)
    Correspondence. 1932, 1935, 1937- 1938
  - Agreement and Strike file: Manufacturers' Railroad - Settlement of time rules, 1939-1940 (Box 30, Folder 62)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Manufacturers' Railroad - Miscellaneous, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 63)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Manufacturer's Railroad - Yardmasters assignment, 1941-1942 (Box 30, Folder 64)
- Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (Michigan Central) (Box 31)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Agreements, wages, rules and work schedule, 1917-1922 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Correspondence. 1911, 1917, 1919, 1922
  - Agreement and Strike file: Michigan Central - Correspondence on Beaver Mine Run, 1918-1919 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Switchmen's Union of North America versus Michigan City of Michigan Central, 1919 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1919-1923 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Request for wage reductions, 1921-1923 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Case of G.W. Thompson, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Agreement and strike file: Michigan Central - Pension case of Joseph Maltby, 1923-1925 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    6a. Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Memorandum and correspondence, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Wage negotiations, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Wages and working conditions, miscellaneous correspondence, 1926-1927 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Wages and rules demands, agreement, 1926 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Seniority case at Jackson, Michigan, 1927-1929 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1928 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Agreement, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1930 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Agreements, 1930-1931 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Indiana Harbor Belt situation, 1931-1932 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Correspondence, 1931-1933 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Pringle case, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Pringle case, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    Correspondence. January-October 1933
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Pringle Case, 1934 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    Correspondence. August-September 1934
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1932-1938 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Meeting between New York City and Michigan Central, men requested, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    Correspondence. January-February 1932
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Minutes of meeting Michigan Central and New York City, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Correspondence. February 1932
  - Agreement and Strike file: Michigan Central - Report from General Committee of Switchmen's Union of North America, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    Correspondence. March 1932
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Continued meetings between New York City and Michigan Central, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    Correspondence. April 1932.
  - Agreement and Strike file: Michigan Central - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    May 1932
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Meetings and correspondence regarding partial consolidation, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    Correspondence. May 1932
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Continued talks on consolidation, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    Correspondence. June 1932
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Toledo and Michigan Central Dispute, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    Correspondence. August-October 1932
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    Correspondence. August 1932.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    Correspondence. September 1932
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Protesting work policies, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Continued controversy, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    Correspondence. October 1932.
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Correspondence on consolidation, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    Correspondence. October 1932
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Consolidation, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    Correspondence. November 1932
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Equity agreement, 1932-1933 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Michigan Central - Correspondence plus agreement of 1938, 1933-1939 (Box 31, Folder 43)